http://www.thepawsmahal.com/privacy-shipping-returns/

Loading... Please wait...
Gift Certificates
Compare (0)
There are no items selected for comparison.
Compare Items
Reset
My Account
Sign In
Forgot your password?
View Messages ()
View Order Status
Completed
Return Requests
Your Address Book
Wish Lists ()
Privacy Policy
The Paws Mahal respects your privacy. While using our website, you may provide us with information that enables us to provide you with enhanced services. This online privacy policy describes how we use and protect the individual identifying information that you share with us and enables us to identify you, such as your e-mail address, name, title, and mailing address.
We urge you at all times to use caution when providing individual identifying information, and suggest that you read the information provided by the Federal Trade Commission on Consumer Information Security.
Information Collection, Use In general, you can visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. As a necessity, however, we collect individual identification (i.e., full name, e-mail address, phone, etc.) when you complete one of our information requests or product ordering forms and use these details to professionally respond to your needs.
We may use the information you volunteer to notify you from time to time about new services and products, and about updates to our existing products. You may opt out of receiving any such correspondence via email to cherie @ thepawsmahal.com.
Information Sharing, Disclosure We will not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to others unless we have your explicit permission or are required by law.
Security No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure. Although we are committed to protecting your personal information, The Paws Mahal cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you send to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Only authorized employees will have access to your personal information and such access is limited to a need-to-know basis.
Our online store supplies you with a secure session within our shopping checkout process. You will notice a padlock icon on the base of your browser when you enter through to the checkout. This indicates that all information entered in the session is secure. Your credit card information is safe. Our online system automatically encrypts all your details using the latest SSL encryption standard. Payments may be made using Visa, Mastercard, Bankcard, American Express and Diners. If you prefer to order using a bank check or money order, please contact us so we can complete your order.
Related Website Links As an informational resource only, The Paws Mahal may provide you with links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites and we do not endorse them or make any representations about them or any information, services, products, or materials found on them. If you decide to access any of the third party sites through links, we strongly encourage you to read their privacy statements.
Return Policy
The Paws Mahal recognizes that our customers may at times need to return merchandise. We stand behind the products we represent on our site. We do, however, request that you adhere to the following guidelines for returning merchandise.
Special order merchandise is non-returnable unless damaged in shipment. Should damage occur, you must notify us immediately via email or phone.
Orders cancelled prior to fulfillment will incur a $10 processing/handling fee.
If you refuse delivery of a shipment, you will be responsible for the cost of outbound shipping, return shipping and any re-stocking fees involved.
We expect you to do your part: measure your pet to be sure it will fit in the carrier, tote or item of clothing you are ordering. We are very exacting with our measurements in our listings and expect you to be sure what you order will fit. Fluffy hair & long hair should be considered when choosing a garment size for your pet: perhaps one size up would be a better fit.
If a return is deemed necessary, we must be notified within 3 business days of order receipt. Our shipping & handling charges are non-refundable. Return shipping costs are your responsibility. The returned item will be inspected when we receive it back. We cannot credit or exchange items that are worn, damaged, soiled or not in the original/undamaged packaging. Items deemed in re-sale condition are subject to re-stocking fees which are manufacturer specific and will be subtracted from your return credit. We will not accept damaged/used items, items that are not in their original condition, items not returned in their original/undamaged packaging, or items with missing parts.
Many of our items are sent directly from the manufacturer. Each of them has their own return policy. Some do not allow returns, while some require a re-stocking fee. If you are ordering items that are size specific, such as clothing and beds/crates, be sure to measure accurately to avoid disappointment and additional fees involved with returning items for replacement. Shipping & handing costs & return shipping fees are your responsibility. Pooch Pad products are not returnable.
You may return defective items within five (5) business days from receipt of shipment, but not thereafter, provided the item(s) is/are unused, unworn, undamaged and they are returned and received in the original/undamaged packaging. Health regulations do not allow pet carrier bags and clothing to be returned.
All returns to the Paws Mahal must be pre-authorized by emailing us: cherie@thepawsmahal.com. A Return Authorization Number will be provided to you, along with procedures to follow to complete the return process. Please be advised that all returns must be in their original, undamaged condition, never used or worn by a pet, and be returned in its original, undamaged packaging/container(s), able to be placed on a shelf for re-sale. Any product authorized for return that is not deemed defective or not in it's original/undamaged packaging will be subject to a restocking fee of 10-30% (depending on the manufacturer) for items you ordered incorrectly (such as size). Shipping & handling charges are non-refundable. It is your responsibility to ensure the size you order matches the measurements in the product listing. Measure….measure…measure before making your selections because returns are expensive!
If we made an error in shipment or the shipment was received damaged, please notify us within 24 hours of receipt. When you receive your shipment, please check your boxes for damage before opening them. If there is evidence of tampering or damage, please refuse the shipment or open the box with the shipper present in case it has to be returned and a claim filed. Please keep the original container and all packing materials for return shipment if you do not refuse delivery.
We strongly urge you to insure your returns for the full retail value. This protects you from financial loss should the returned item be damaged in transit by your carrier. We will not accept returned items damaged during shipment or un-authorized returns.
Sign up for our newsletter
Contact Info
The Paws Mahal
650 South Hwy. 27
Suite 5-301
Somerset, KY 42503
941-375-3806
orders@thepawsmahal.com
Custom eCommerce Website by LunaseaMedia Productions, Inc.
Copyright 2020 The Paws Mahal. All Rights Reserved.
Sitemap | Policies
View Cart
Go To Checkout
